=Summer In Love=
= الصيف في الحب =
=Episode 12= (Can We Change The Ending?)
= الحلقة 12 = (هل يمكننا تغيير النهاية؟)
Student, are you okay?
طالب ، هل أنت بخير؟
Call 120.
اتصل على 120.
Yes.
نعم.
(Ambulance)
(سياره اسعاف)
Will he die?
هل سيموت؟
I can't tell.
لا استطيع ان اقول.
Looking at what happened,
بالنظر إلى ما حدث ،
he should at least be handicapped.
يجب أن يكون على الأقل معاق.
What did he tell you just now?
ماذا قال لك الآن؟
No matter what he said,
مهما قال ،
don't believe him.
لا تصدقه.
You know about this?
هل تعلم عن هذا؟
He came here as well?
أتى هنا أيضا؟
Yes.
نعم.
He's looked for me.
لقد بحث عني.
Didn he do anything to you?
ألم يفعل لك أي شيء؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
He won't do anything
لن يفعل أي شيء
in the campus.
في الحرم الجامعي.
How did he come here?
كيف اتى الى هنا؟
Supposedly
يفترض
we've changed many things.
لقد غيرنا أشياء كثيرة.
Why is he here to pester us?
لماذا هو هنا ليضايقنا؟
Have you heard of
هل سمعت عن
the grandfather paradox?
مفارقة الجد؟
What does it mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
What we have changed here
ما تغيرنا هنا
might not be able to affect
قد لا يكون قادرًا على التأثير
the future that has happened.
المستقبل الذي حدث.
But things have really changed.
لكن الأمور تغيرت بالفعل.
My father,
ابي،
Xiaoyu,
شياويو
you and I.
أنت وأنا.
We have changed many things,
لقد غيرنا أشياء كثيرة ،
but not
لكن لا
the ending.
النهاية.
Since we can't change it,
بما أننا لا نستطيع تغييره ،
let's live the current life well.
دعونا نعيش الحياة الحالية بشكل جيد.
It makes sense.
يبدو الأمر معقولا.
Yes.
نعم.
We're young.
كان الشباب.
- Yes. - There's nothing to be afraid of.
- نعم.  - لا يوجد شيء تخاف منه.
That's right.
صحيح.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
لا يوجد شيء تخاف منه.
Like this?
مثله؟
(Camera)
(آلة تصوير)
Hurry. Give it to me.
عجل.  اعطني اياه.
- Isn't it cute? - Give it to me.
- أليس لطيف؟  - اعطني اياه.
(Adult)
(بالغ)
He's not in danger anymore,
لم يعد في خطر بعد الآن ،
but it seems like his brain
لكن يبدو أنه عقله
has been injured before.
أصيب من قبل.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
It's hard to explain.
يصعب شرحه.
Let me put it this way.
اسمحوا لي أن أطرح السؤال بهذه الطريقة.
His mental health is not stable.
صحته العقلية غير مستقرة.
Why not you take him to the psychiatry?
لماذا لا تأخذه إلى الطب النفسي؟
We
نحن
have never encountered this before.
لم نواجه هذا من قبل.
We need to monitor him.
نحن بحاجة إلى مراقبته.
(Could what he said last night be true?)
(هل يمكن أن يكون ما قاله الليلة الماضية صحيحًا؟)
Doctor,
طبيب،
can we talk outside?
ممكن نتكلم بالخارج
Okay.
تمام.
Doctor,
طبيب،
you said that
انت قلت ذلك
before Xin had the accident,
قبل وقوع الحادث ،
he had been
انه كان
in a coma?
في غيبوبة؟
You can say that.
تستطيع قول ذلك.
His consciousness is not clear.
وعيه غير واضح.
Isn't that mental illness?
أليس هذا مرض عقلي؟
Doctor,
طبيب،
please keep this a secret for me.
من فضلك ابق هذا سرا بالنسبة لي.
My son
ابني
can't be diagnosed as a mental patient.
لا يمكن تشخيصه كمريض عقلي.
You can't say that.
لا يمكنك قول ذلك.
(Girls Dorm Building Two)
(مبنى سكن البنات الثاني)
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Didn't you say
لم تقل
we need to live the current life well?
نحن بحاجة إلى أن نعيش الحياة الحالية بشكل جيد؟
Yes.
نعم.
Then?
ثم؟
(Jay Chou's concert ticket)
(تذكرة حفلة جاي تشو)
Jay Chou?
جاي تشو؟
How did you get these?
كيف حصلت على هؤلاء؟
It's my biggest regret that
إنه أسفي الأكبر على ذلك
I didn't get to go to Jay Chou's concert.
لم أتمكن من الذهاب إلى حفلة جاي تشو.
Yes?
نعم؟
No,
لا،
just one of the regrets.
مجرد واحدة من الأسف.
My biggest regret
أسفي الأكبر
is someone else.
هو شخص آخر.
Jay Chou!
جاي تشو!
Jay Chou, you're my god!
جاي تشو ، أنت إلهي!
I'll go back now.
سأعود الآن.
Look at her boyfriend.
انظر إلى صديقها.
He's so thoughtful.
إنه عميق التفكير.
Let's break up.
لننفصل.
Darling.
محبوب.
You...
أنت...
You're terrible.
كنت الرهيب.
Why did you show off Jay Chou?
لماذا تباهت بجاي تشو؟
Give me my girlfriend back!
أعطني صديقتي مرة أخرى!
Xia He treats you like this
شيا هو يعاملك مثل هذا
because you've hurt him before.
لأنك آذيته من قبل.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
When did I ever hurt him?
متى آذيته؟
Not now,
ليس الآن،
but in the future.
لكن في المستقبل.
You'll hurt him badly in the future.
سوف تؤذيه بشدة في المستقبل.
That's why he doesn't want to have anything to do with you.
لهذا السبب لا يريد أن يفعل أي شيء معك.
We haven't met for two days
لم نلتقي منذ يومين
and you've become crazy.
وأنت مجنون.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
10 years later,
بعد 10 سنوات ،
you'll become his wife.
ستصبح زوجته.
Not only have you cheated on him,
ليس فقط أنك خدعته ،
you've even dumped him after he got broke
حتى أنك تخلت عنه بعد أن انفصل
and got together with me.
وقابلتني.
Let go of me.
ترك لي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You'll marry Xia He.
سوف تتزوج شيا هي.
Remember.
يتذكر.
This is destiny.
هذا هو القدر.
You can't run away from it.
لا يمكنك الهروب منه.
Father?
أب؟
May I know
هل لي أن أعلم
where is the gynecology and obstetrics?
اين طب النساء والتوليد؟
Turn left in front there.
انعطف يسارًا في الأمام هناك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Here.
هنا.
It's here.
إنه هنا.
Go in.
أدخل.
Father.
أب.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
I'm in the office.
أنا في المكتب.
What's wrong, Shanshan?
ما بك يا شانشان؟
Who is there with you?
من معك هناك؟
I'm having a meeting with my colleagues.
لدي اجتماع مع زملائي.
Is there anything?
هل يوجد أي شئ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
(International Medical Centre)
(المركز الطبي الدولي)
Father.
أب.
Shanshan.
شانشان.
You...
أنت...
Aren't you having a meeting in the office?
ألا تقابل في المكتب؟
Who is this?
من هذا؟
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
She's not...
هي ليست...
You're cheating on my mother.
أنت تخون والدتي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Shanshan, what are you doing?
شانشان ، ماذا تفعل؟
I want to take the picture of your ugly faces
أريد أن ألتقط صورة لوجوهك القبيحة
to show my mother.
لتظهر والدتي.
Gao,
جاو
stop him.
أوقفوه.
Or I'll die in front of you.
أو سأموت أمامك.
Since you want to die,
بما أنك تريد أن تموت ،
just go and die.
فقط اذهب و مت.